<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GameOfCards</string>

    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_host">HostActivity</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_join">JoinActivity</string>

    <string-array name="deal_exactly">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>9</item>
        <item>10</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="card_array">
        <item>ace</item>
        <item>two</item>
        <item>three</item>
        <item>four</item>
        <item>five</item>
        <item>six</item>
        <item>seven</item>
        <item>eight</item>
        <item>nine</item>
        <item>ten</item>
        <item>jack</item>
        <item>queen</item>
        <item>king</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="info_content">Thank you for downloading our Game of Cards app. We hope you are happy with your download. The app has been developed by Rohit Ramkumar (<a href="mailto:rohitramkumar308@gmail.com">rohitramkumar308@gmail.com</a>), Shivank Malik (<a href="mailto:shivankmalik@gmail.com">shivankmalik@gmail.com</a>) and Kunal Shrivastava (<a href="mailto:knlshrvstv@gmail.com">knlshrvstv@gmail.com</a>).\n\nThe way this app works has been described here. One of the player acts as host of the game and this player MUST have its hotspot on before the start of the app. The other players join to this hotspot before starting the game. The host player sees the "Host game" screen while the other players meet with the "Join game" screen. The host enters the number of players in order to host the game. This number is crucial to restrict the number of players in the game (maximum is 6). So, if the total number of players are 3 (including the host), then the host must enter 2 in the "Number of players" field.\n\nThe essence of the app is that there are no rules and the deck can be customized in more ways than one. Once the game begins after all the players and joined the game, the host gets the option to deal the cards from the deck during the game.\n\nWe do thoroughly test our apps, but it is impossible to test every phone/option combination. If you feel something is not working correctly with your app, please contact us directly at any of the aforementioned email address so that we can help you or fix a bug and get a new release out for all to benefit. And if you love our app, please post a review in the app store. Thank you!​</string>


    <string name="title_activity_splash_screen">SplashScreenActivity</string>
</resources>
